=No.9 Hunter=
=Episode 21=
(Lanruo Hall)
Fengniang?
One is already more than enough.
Why bring another one back?
Lanruo Hall isn't a shelter.
We don't take in just anyone.
Lanxi,
have you ever heard of
Heavenly Justice,
Underworld Soul,
and Tearless Tear?
Why do you ask about these?
I am going to kill Yu Linjun.
You're going to slay his Lord?
Shh.
Ziyan,
I don't care
where you heard such nonsense,
But Yu Linjun
is not someone you or I can fight.
If you fail...
I'm just his next meal,
a caged demon.
Even if I don't kill him,
he will kill me eventually.
I don't know
Heavenly Justice and Tearless Tear.
But the Underworld Soul...
it's the heart-soul of someone
brought back from death.
Right now, I'm the only one who has it.
I can give it to you.
Lanxi,
you're not going to stop me?
I've already died once.
When my own sister
is in need,
how could I stand by and do nothing?
And let an outsider interfere?
Let's split up.
We'll track down
the other two ingredients.
Young Taoist, stay alive.
Ziyan.
Hmm.
This little servant of yours
is interesting.
Bring him to my room tonight.
He is rather handsome.
With some training...
Lanxi.
Hmm.
Isn't my company enough for you?
He is merely a servant.
He is unworthy of you.
There are better ones
for you to choose from.
It is fine, Yuanchu.
She's just lost her memory.
We'll gather what we need first,
then kill Yu Linjun and mend the sky.
Heavenly Justice
needs a pure body as its vessel.
Once you begin,
your heart and mind
must be free of all distraction.
As for Tearless Tear...
- Shangguan Piaopiao.
Who dares call me by my name?
Hahaha.
Godmother.
Mother didn't come all this way
just because you missed me, did you?
My dear daughter.
I heard our Lord
has taken a liking to you,
making you Demon Queen.
I couldn't be happier for you.
(It seems Yu Linjun)
(means to use)
(the bond between mother and daughter)
(to make my Love Flower bloom.)
(Fine.)
(I'll use this chance)
(to get the Tearless Tear.)
You little demon brat.
Are you scheming to steal my position
as Madam of Lanruo Hall?
You'd better make it worth my while.
What are you saying?
Isn't my money yours?
If one day,
I find someone I love,
what dowry will you give me
for my wedding, mother?
Oh, seriously,
you have learned to bargain with me.
You really have grown up.
Tell me, what do you want?
It's simple.
One tear from you.
Insolent!
I am a Lishuo Rabbit Demon.
I was born without tears.
You little brat.
You've gotten too bold.
More disrespectful by the day!
(Godmother used the Spirit-Calling Art)
(to enter my illusion.)
(Why did that young Taoist appear)
(in my Demon Essence Memory?)
(You little demon brat,)
(Demon Essence Memories never lie.)
(Think carefully.)
(Would you really
bloom with love for Yu Linjun?)
How did you get into my illusion?
If Godmother finds out,
you're dead.
Get out now.
(Just now in the illusion,)
(my Love Flower bloomed.)
(Could this young Taoist really be...)
No man has ever walked out
of Godmother's illusion alive.
My sister must be protecting you.
You little servant,
how did you bewitch my sister?
Excuse me, miss.
Hey!
That's not quite right.
They are proper husband and wife.
Husband and wife?
I have never heard Ziyan mention this.
They love each other,
married in heart.
We outsiders cannot compare.
If she hadn't lost her memory,
she'd never marry that freak Yu Linjun.
(Such strange demon energy.)
(Could she really come back from death?)
Words are cheap.
Don't try to fool me.
True
or false,
only time will tell.
Gaining Tearless Tear
won't be easy.
Let's help you
gather Heavenly Justice first.
It needs a pure body as its vessel.
Before, Yuanchu could refine it
in moments.
But now he's lost all his power,
corrupted by foul energy.
He may not be able to hold it.
Unless we find a place
thick with foul energy.
Use foulness to cleanse foulness.
When it peaks, it reverses.
Then it can be condensed.
The Void Realm.
The Uncrossable Ferry
before Yu Linjun's Ninghua Palace.
To reach Ninghua Palace,
one must cross the Uncrossable Ferry.
If your demon power isn't strong enough,
you'll die, your soul
sinking into the depths forever.
You're just a mortal.
You will surely die.
Don't be afraid, Yuanchu.
I'm here.
If you sink to the bottom,
I'll drink every last drop of that water
to pull you out.
What is this?
It's made from the Essence
of hundreds of demons.
If you cannot cross the lake,
crush this,
it'll get you out safely.
Don't misunderstand.
I just don't want you to die
and lose my cure.
You have only one chance.
Cross the Ferry,
and you'll obtain Heavenly Justice.
I will cross it.
Wait for me.
Hmm.
The foul energy
will strip away his senses.
Right now, his eyes, ears,
nose and mouth
are being torn away in agony.
Yuanchu!
I believe in him.
(Ziyan,)
(so this is the pain)
(you walked through.)
(In this way,)
(I have shared all of your life.)
(I have no regrets in this life.)
Yuanchu!
Don't scare me!
(Why does my heart ache)
(watching him in pain?)
Yuanchu!
Heavenly Justice is complete.
Senior.
I am back.
♪I drink the rain of this mortal world,
and seek the path I chose♪
♪How much sorrow and joy have I known?♪
♪With this flesh and blood,
I chase the distant light♪
♪Just to see clearly
the memories of this drifting life♪
♪Let the wind sweep away
this heavy air of sorrow♪
♪Do not forget the tangled paths
that you and I have crossed♪
♪Let towering waves come crashing down,
I'll fight against the tide♪
♪I shatter
the hollow fate they wrote for me♪
♪With a heart free of regret,
I'll face the heavens and earth♪